Madison Haskins

Box 13491 915 E. Market Ave Searcy, AR 72149 (479) 409-6515

mhaskins@harding.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/madisonhaskins

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Takes leadership, good communicator, and efficient in group settings. Meets deadlines in timely manner, open to learn new skills on the job, excels in problem solving. Experience with directly contacting customers, very experienced in technology, focuses on improvements that can be made.

EDUCATION

HARDING UNIVERSITY- SEARCY, ARKANSAS

Fall 2014 - Spring 2018

Bachelor of Business Administration, Management of Information Systems, Minor, Computer Science Overall GPA: 3.58

HONORS AND ACTIVITIES

Dean's List (2014 - 2017)

Harding University Honors Student

Recipient of Associated Women for Harding scholarship

Member of the Harding University Association for Information Systems

EAST National Founder's Award recipient (2013)

Merchandise, Activities Director, Historian, Athletic Director, and Vice President for Chi Omega Pi (social club)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software: Visual Studios, Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google based software

Operating Systems: Windows Vista, 7, 8, and 10, Mac OS X, Chrome OS **Programming:** C++, Visual Basic, HTML5, CSS, php, JavaScript, Python

On-The-Job Experience: Microsoft Access and Excel, AV and classroom technologies

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HARDING UNIVERSITY Searcy, AR

January 2015 - Present

Classroom Technology and Labs - E-Learning

Student Technician

Provided additional assistance in maintenance and technical support of classroom technology. Duties included troubleshooting audio-video equipment (projector, switcher, splitter, computer/laptop connections, SmartBoards, SP controls/Crestron systems, etc.). Interacted with professors to solve the problems, sometimes under pressure.

HARDING UNIVERSITY Searcy, AR

August 2015 - Present

Student Computing - DormNet

DormNet Assistant

Provided assistance in maintenance and technical support of student technology. Duties included troubleshooting internet connection, installing and running anti-virus to clean computers, and interacting with student body over phone and face-to-face.

Senior DormNet Assistant – 2016 - Current

Fulfilling the duties of a regular DormNet Assistant while also being involved in the interviewing processes for new student workers, training them, and being constantly in contact in case of emergency while also overseeing the day-to-day processes of the DormNet help desk.

MOSS ADAMS Portland, OR

Moss Adams Advisory Services

June – August 2017

IT Audit Intern

Performed SOC compliance jobs supporting multiple clients in the public sector as well as in the business services, technology, and government sectors, while demonstrating quality and fast turnaround time. Led and participated in client interviews for walkthroughs and testing of IT General Controls, application controls, key reports, interfaces, SOC reports, implementation reviews, ERP and infrastructure assessments. Collaborated with team members to plan and develop work program timelines, risk assessments, and other planning documents. Served as a fieldwork contributor by traveling to customer site, supporting the daily progress of fieldwork, and informing supervisors of engagement status.